Wassila Chtioui



? Tunis, Tunisia

■ wassila.chtioui@edu.isetcom.tn

\$\sqrt{58845163} # 11/11/2001

in Wassila Chtioui 🕠 Wassila

Profile

Student in Network and Telecommunication engineering at ISET'COM, Cyber Security enthusiast, I spend time exploring new innovations and learning new technologies.

I enjoy taking part in hacking and pentesting competitions: CTF (Capture The Flag contests). Skilled and experienced in information security, various programming languages.

Awards

1st place ISET Innovation

2021

1st Place in ISET Innovation Preselection Contest (2IA)

Skills

Web Development (HTML/CSS, Angular, Ionic, .NET Framework, SQL Server),
Programming (Java, C, C#, Python),
Networking (Wireshark, Packet Tracer, CISCO),
Linux Administration,
OWASP Mobile Security

Interests

Music (Violonist), CTF, Painting, Gymnastic

Languages

Arabic	•	•	•	•	•
English TOEFL	•	•	•	•	•
French	•	•	•	•	

Education

License in Network and Telecommunication, *ISET'COM*2020 – 2023 | Tunis, Tunisia

Certificates

ITU Generation Connect Arab Youth Group

Ø

International Telecommunication Union

Professional Experience

Cyber Security Intern, Axe Finance 08/2021 – present | Tunis, Tunisia Implementing OWASP Top 10 Mobile Security in a banking application.

Network Intern, CNAM

07/2021 – 08/2021 | Tunis, Tunisia

Usage of CISCO CLI and Packet Tracer to configure VLAN and routers and Wireshark for monitoring traffic.

Projects

Wristband For Geolocation Tracking

02/2021 - present

An aspiring startup working on the usage of LoraWan Technology to seize its advantage in battery economy in order to track the location in real time for people suffering from Alzheimer.

Organisations

Engineers Spark, *Chairwoman* 2021 – present

Carthage Symphony Orchestra

2020 - present

Securinets National Association

2020 - present

HackLock, *Project Manager* 02/2021